The Christmas Parade is a drama, family, tv movie
film directed by Jonathan Wright.
A popular network morning host finds herself humiliated on the
air by her fiancé and disappears to a small town.
While there, she helps a budding artist save a community art center for the town's
kids, by helping them with their float for the annual Christmas Parade.
Hayley Temple, played by AnnaLynne McCord.
Beck Thomas, played by Jefferson Brown.
Jason Keppler, played by Drew Scott.
Monica, played by Jennifer Gibson.
Zach, played by Christian Martyn.
Kelsey, played by Katherine Forrester.
On November 21, 2021, Darrell Edward Brooks Jr.
drove a sport utility vehicle (SUV) through the annual Christmas parade in Waukesha,
Wisconsin, United States, killing six people and injuring 62 others.
The parade was live-streamed, and other attendees captured the
incident on videos later posted to social media.
Brooks, who had been reportedly diagnosed with bipolar disorder as a child, had an extensive
criminal record including several charges of sex crimes and domestic violence.
He pleaded not guilty to six counts of first-degree
intentional homicide and 70 additional charges.
He chose to represent himself at his trial, which began on October 3, 2022.
Brooks presented pseudolegal arguments from the sovereign citizen movement and was repeatedly
removed from the courtroom for failing to comply with decorum and courtesy.
On October 26, 2022, a jury found Brooks guilty on all 76 charges.
On November 16, 2022, he was sentenced to six consecutive life sentences without the
possibility of parole, plus an additional 762.5 years to be served consecutively.
The film explores themes of small town, holiday, christmas, christmas parade.
The tone is emotional.